Previously:
- Who says that in the middle of sex?
I don't know.
It was the heat of the moment.
No, the heat of the moment is,
"Oh, yeah, just like that."
Not, "Will you marry me?"
NASA really wants my telescope up
on the Space Station...
...so they're putting me
on an earlier launch.
- When?
- A week from Friday.
What? But we're getting married
that Sunday.
You're right. I can't go to space.
l have to get married.
No one can say that's not a good reason.
I'll call them back.
- Have the wedding when you get back.
- Your dad's gonna be furious.
There's no way he's gonna let us
postpone this wedding. Well, we tried.
I'll talk to him.
He won't say no to his little girl.
No, l... I should talk to him,
you know, man-to-man.
All right, look, I'm gonna level with you.
I'm terrified about going into space.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)You know,
what if I don't make it back?